Trigger navigation

    SERVICES
    
    * Email Validation
        
    * [Email Validation](https://www.zerobounce.net/services/email-validation/ "Clean your email lists.")Clean your email list. Reach your customers
    * [Email Activity Data](https://www.zerobounce.net/services/activity-data/ "Find and target your active email subscribers.")Discover your most active subscribers
    * [Email Score](https://www.zerobounce.net/services/email-scoring/ "Email scoring validates catch-all emails.")AI email list analysis for in-depth insight
    * [Email Finder](https://www.zerobounce.net/services/email-finder/ "Email Finder")Find new valid email addresses
    
    * Email Deliverability
        
    * [Email Warmup](https://www.zerobounce.net/services/email-warmup/ "Email Warmup")Boost your inbox placement
    * [DMARC monitor](https://www.zerobounce.net/services/dmarc-monitor/ "DMARC monitor")Real-time multi-domain DMARC monitoring
    * [Blacklist Monitor](https://www.zerobounce.net/services/blacklist-monitoring/ "Get notifications on your email blacklist status.")Real-time blacklist monitoring
    * [Inbox Placement Test](https://www.zerobounce.net/services/inbox-placement-test/ "Test for the best email deliverability.")Test email address deliverability
    * [Email Server Tester Tool](https://www.zerobounce.net/services/email-server-test/ "Test for the best email deliverability.")Diagnose email server issues
    * [Email Deliverability Toolkit](https://www.zerobounce.net/email-deliverability-tools/ "Email Deliverability Toolkit")Every tool; one convenient package
    
    API
    
    * FREE TOOLS

    Solutions

    SUPPORT

    API

    EMAIL TYPES

    Email Deliverability

    * 
        
        Events

* 
    
    * **English**

* Privacy Policy
* Website Terms

Last updated: March 22, 2024

Privacy Policy
==============

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for [www.zerobounce.net](https://www.zerobounce.net/ "Homepage") (the “Site”), including ZeroBounce’s policies on the collection, use, and disclosure of information in connection with Your use of the Site and any related email validation_ⓘ__A process that determines if an email address uses valid syntax, exists on a given domain, and is configured to receive incoming email messages_ services (the “Services”). When You access or use the Site or the Services, You agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

PARTICIPATION IN EU-U.S. DATA PRIVACY FRAMEWORK AND U.K. EXTENSION AND SWISS-U.S. DATA PRIVACY FRAMEWORK
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Hertza L.L.C. and its divisions/the covered entities, including ZeroBounce, complies with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF), the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce. Hertza L.L.C. and its divisions/the covered entities, including ZeroBounce, have certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that they adhere to the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (EU-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from the European Union in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and from the United Kingdom (and Gibraltar) in reliance on the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF. Hertza L.L.C. and its divisions/the covered entities, including ZeroBounce, have certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that they adhere to the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from Switzerland in reliance on the Swiss-U.S. DPF. If there is any conflict between the terms in this Privacy Policy and the EU-U.S. DPF Principles and/or the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles, the Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Data Privacy Framework (DPF) program, and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/).

We collect the types of personal data identified under the “Personal Information Collected”. We collect and use such personal information for the purposes identified under the same heading. The types of third parties to which we disclose personal information, and the purposes for such disclosure are also noted above under the same heading.

Pursuant to the Data Privacy Frameworks, EU, UK, and Swiss individuals have the right to obtain our confirmation of whether we maintain personal information relating to You in the United States. Upon request, we will provide You with access to the personal information that we hold about You. You may also correct, amend, or delete the personal information we hold about You. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data transferred to the United States under the Data Privacy Frameworks, should direct their query by clicking on the "Contact Us" link on the bottom of the Site. If requested to remove data, we will respond within a reasonable timeframe.

We will provide an individual opt-out choice, or opt-in for sensitive data, before we share Your data with third parties other than our agents, or before we use it for a purpose other than which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized. To request to limit the use and disclosure of Your personal information, please submit a written request by clicking on the "Contact Us" link on the bottom of the Site.

In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

ZeroBounce’s accountability for personal data that it receives in the United States under the Data Privacy Frameworks and subsequently transfers to a third party is described in the Data Privacy Framework Principles. In particular, ZeroBounce remains responsible and liable under the Data Privacy Framework Principles if third-party agents that it engages to process personal data on its behalf do so in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless ZeroBounce proves that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES
--------------------------------

#### Traffic Data Collected

ZeroBounce may store information that Your computer provides to us in connection with Your use of the Site and/or Services, such as: 1) IP address; 2) domain servers; 3) type of computer or device accessing the Site; 4) types of web browsers used to access the Site; 5) Internet service provider (ISP); and 6) information based on the above such as Your geographic region based on Your IP address and/or web browser type and area code and zip code associated with Your web server (collectively, “Traffic Data”). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify You but is helpful for marketing purposes or for improving Your experience on the Site. ZeroBounce may also store usage data such as the date and time the Site and Services are accessed, clickstream data, behavioral data like opens and clicks, and what information and files have been downloaded.

### Cookie Policy

#### What are cookies?

When You visit the Site or otherwise interact with the Services, ZeroBounce may send one or more “cookies” to Your computer. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers stored on Your computer through Your web browser and are used by most websites to record user activity and to personalize Your web experience. Some cookies may facilitate Site features for enhanced performance and functionality such as remembering preferences, analyzing usage for Site optimization, and providing custom content. The length of time a cookie stays on Your device varies depending on the type of cookie.

#### What cookies does ZeroBounce use on the Site and why?

EU legislation requires websites to inform users when cookies are in use. Please note that strictly necessary cookies are being used by default, and you have consented to the use of such cookies upon your acceptance of the cookie consent banner language incorporated on our Site. We collect user consent to cookies every twelve months on our Site. We use the following types of cookies, including third party cookies, and similar technologies on this Site:

#### Strictly necessary cookies

Strictly necessary cookies are essential for us to deliver the Site and related Services to You securely and in compliance with applicable law and cannot be disabled. Such strictly necessary cookies include third party cookies, including but not limited to those from Amazon Web Services, Cloudflare, Okta, Stripe, and Zendesk. Without the strictly necessary cookies, you would be unable to sign in to Your ZeroBounce account and access the Services through the Site.

#### Targeting or advertising cookies

Targeting or advertising cookies help us deliver and track ads, and deliver relevant content for you. Such targeting or advertising cookies include third party cookies, including but not limited to those from Google/GoogleAdSense and Microsoft Bing. You may choose to disable these types of cookies.

ZeroBounce may link the information it stores in cookies to any Personal Information You submit through the Site or Services. ZeroBounce utilizes both session cookies, which remain active on Your web browser until closed, and persistent cookies, which are stored in Your web browser for a longer period of time, until they expire or are deleted.

#### Enabling and disabling cookies

To check to see if cookies are enabled on Your device, please follow the steps below. Alternatively, view Your browser’s help pages or information on how to manage cookies at: [https://www.allaboutcookies.org](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/), which contains comprehensive information on cookies on a wide variety of browsers. You can also find details on how to delete cookies from Your computer. To understand these settings, the following links may be helpful, or You can use the “help” option in Your browser for more details:

#### Cookie settings in Internet Explorer:  
[https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-10](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-10)

#### Cookie settings in Firefox:  
[https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/cookies-information-websites-store-on-your-computer?redirectlocale=en-US&redirectslug=Cookies](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/cookies-information-websites-store-on-your-computer?redirectlocale=en-US&redirectslug=Cookies)

#### Cookie settings in Chrome:  
[https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en&ref\_topic=14666](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en&ref_topic=14666)

#### Settings in Safari web and iOs:  
[https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac](https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac)

In addition to the above, Google has developed a Google Analytics opt-out browser add on to prevent the use of Your data by Google Analytics: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout Google Analytics](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

### Personal Information Collected

To the extent that You elect to create an account on the Site, ZeroBounce collects information that You submit in connection Your account (“Personal Information”), including Your full name, email address, the password You select, phone number, company industry, and/or the third party social media account You may select, to sign in to the Services. To the extent that You purchase credits through the Site for the Services, or subscribe to purchase credits, Your credit card/debit card number and related billing information will also be collected. Personal Information such as Your name and email address are used to create a user account for the Site and Services, as well as for ZeroBounce’s advertising and marketing purposes (such as email newsletters) and invoicing.

If You initiate a payment for the Services, ZeroBounce may collect and store Personal Information, as well as any other information provided to us. ZeroBounce encrypts credit card numbers using industry standard technology. This Personal Information may be shared with third parties such as Paypal and/or Stripe to process Your payment(s) for the Services.

We collect Personal Information directly from You via the Site and from Your use and interactions with the Site, including from cookies on the Site. A cookie is a small data text file, which is stored on Your computer’s hard drive (if Your web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify You to us. Cookies record user activity and personalize Your Site experience. To the extent that You receive electronic communications from us such as our email newsletters and/or email updates, we also collect information on whether You viewed the email communications, and clicked on any links within such email communications, through the use of cookies and tracking pixels. Your Personal information may also be collected from, shared with, and used by our third party advertising partners, including for purposes of optimizing and targeting of ad content.

To the extent that You elect to submit a Google Sheet containing Personal Information in conjunction with the Services, You understand that such information is shared with Google through Your use of such. Information uploaded to the Site or otherwise submitted to ZeroBounce in conjunction with the Services, including but not limited to CSV or TXT files, or through Google Sheets, may be stored encrypted with a password for a period of thirty (30) days; however, You have the option to manually delete such information through the Customer dashboard. For non-enterprise customers, ZeroBounce may cache and store results generated through the Services; however, non-enterprise customers may elect to opt-out by notifying ZeroBounce of such request. For enterprise customers, caching and storage of results generated through the Services is disabled unless such customer has otherwise agreed.

ZeroBounce’s use and transfer to any other app of information received from Google APIs will adhere to [Google API Services User Data Policy,](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy#additional_requirements_for_specific_api_scopes) including the Limited Use requirements.

ZeroBounce commits to subject all Personal Information received from the European Union and, as applicable the United Kingdom (and Gibraltar) and/or Switzerland in reliance on the relevant parts of the DPF program . If You register an account and/or provide information to ZeroBounce, You consent to Your Personal Information being collected, used, and stored by ZeroBounce, in accordance with the Terms and Conditions of Use and this Privacy Policy.

### ZeroBounce may use your Personal Information to

* Respond to Your inquiries and fulfill Your requests for Services;
* Send information to You, including information regarding our Services;
* Complete and fulfill Your purchase, for example, to process Your payments, or communicate with You regarding Your purchase;
* Automatically create personalized and automated experiences for You based on Your interactions with our Site;
* Send You marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to You, including via third party platforms;
* Advertise Our Site and Services to You on third party platforms, including targeting;
* Personalize Your experience on the Site or Services;
* Conduct data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention;
* Develop new products and services, or enhance, improve, or modify our products or services; and
* As necessary or appropriate under applicable law, including laws outside Your country of residence; to comply with legal process; to respond to requests from public and government authorities; to enforce our terms and conditions; to protect our operations; to protect our rights, privacy, safety, and/or that of our affiliates, You or others; and to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

We may collect, analyze, and use data derived from Personal Information and/or information collected from or about an individual but which does not identify the individual personally for purposes of operating, analyzing, improving, or marketing the ZeroBounce Services. Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, ZeroBounce will keep Your Personal Information private and will not sell or rent Personal Information to anyone. In cases of onward transfers to third parties, Zero Bounce shall remain liable for any violations of this Privacy Policy and of the DPF Principles.

NOTICE TO UK AND EU RESIDENTS
-----------------------------

Our legal basis for collecting and using Your Personal Information will depend on the Personal Information collected and the specific context in which we collect it. We collect Personal Information when we have Your consent to do so, where we need Your personal information to perform any agreed-upon Services, or where the processing is in our legitimate interests.

OPTING-OUT OF FUTURE CONTACTS AND YOUR CHOICES TO LIMIT THE USE AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Unless You ask us not to, we may contact You via email in the future to tell You about specials, new services, or changes to this Privacy Policy. You may opt-out of receiving promotional email by sending a request for removal by clicking on the “Contact Us” link on the bottom of the Site or by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the email itself. ZeroBounce will try to comply with Your request as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that if You do opt-out of receiving promotional emails from us, ZeroBounce may still send You messages for administrative or other purposes directly relating to Your use of the Services, and You cannot opt-out of receiving those messages.

You can do the following at any time by contacting us via our website:

* See what data, including any Personal Information, we have about You, if any;
* Request access to Your Personal Information;
* Change/correct any data we have about You;
* Have us delete any data we have about You;
* Express any concern You have about our use of Your data;

If You request deletion of Your account, we may need to retain certain Personal Information for recordkeeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that You began prior to requesting such change or deletion. There may also be residual information that will remain within our databases and other records, which will not be removed. We may retain Personal Information for as long as needed to provide the Site and Services, or to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, prevent abuse, and enforce our agreements. To contact ZeroBounce with any inquiries or complaints, including any regarding our Terms, Privacy Policy, or other policy related material, click on the "Contact Us" link on the bottom of the Site.

CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
-------------------------

Although we are not a qualifying “business” under the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”), we voluntarily comply. For information specific to California residents, please review [California Privacy Rights](https://www.zerobounce.net/ca-privacy "California Privacy Rights").

SECURITY
--------

We take precautions to protect Your information. We maintain our Site and Services and all associated data with technical, administrative, and physical safeguards to protect against loss, unauthorized access, destruction, misuse, modification, and improper disclosure.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect Your information offline. Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. If a security breach causes an unauthorized intrusion into our Site or Services that materially affects You or Your Personal Information, we will attempt to notify You as soon as possible.

DATA RETENTION
--------------

We will retain Your Personal Information for as long as needed to provide the Services, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

CROSS-BORDER TRANSFER
---------------------

The Site and Services are controlled by ZeroBounce, which is located in the United States. For customers that specifically elect to utilize ZeroBounce’s API server in the United States: ZeroBounce will process Personal Information in the United States. However, in all other instances, ZeroBounce processes and stores Personal Information in the EU.

Further, to the extent that a ZeroBounce customer transfers Personal Information originating in the EU, UK, or Switzerland, we implement appropriate safeguards, consistent with the laws of the applicable territory. Namely, where transfers are made by ZeroBounce customers in the EU, we incorporate a data processing addendum and the EU standard contractual clauses. Where transfers are made by ZeroBounce customers in the UK, we incorporate a data processing addendum and the UK standard contractual clauses. Unless otherwise agreed by the parties, Your use of the Site and Services is not intended to subject Us to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country, or territory other than that of United States. By using the Site and Services, You consent to the transfer of such information to countries outside of Your country of residence, including the United States and the EU, which may have different data protection rules than those of Your country. To the extent that a non-U.S. resident specifically elects to use utilize ZeroBounce’s API server in the United States, it elects to do so at its own risk.

DISPUTES
--------

Individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Policy, should first contact ZeroBounce by clicking on the "Contact Us" link on the bottom of the Site.

In compliance with the Data Privacy Framework Principles, ZeroBounce commits to resolve complaints about Your privacy and our collection or use of Your personal information transferred to the United States pursuant to the Data Privacy Frameworks. European Union, United Kingdom, and Swiss individuals with DPF inquiries or complaints should first contact ZeroBounce by clicking on the "Contact Us" link on the bottom of the Site.

ZeroBounce has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Data Privacy Framework Principles to a U.S.-based independent dispute resolution mechanism, BBB NATIONAL PROGRAMS. If You do not receive timely acknowledgment of Your complaint, or if Your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [https://www.bbbprograms.org/dpf-complaints](https://www.bbbprograms.org/dpf-complaints) for more information and to file a complaint. This service is provided free of charge to You.

ZeroBounce is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (“FTC”). The FTC has jurisdiction over ZeroBounce’s compliance with the EU-U.S. DPF and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. DPF.

If Your DPF complaint cannot be resolved through the above channels, under certain conditions, You may invoke binding arbitration for some residual claims not resolved by other redress mechanisms. See [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/framework-article/ANNEX-I-introduction](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/framework-article/ANNEX-I-introduction)

CHANGES
-------

ZeroBounce reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy. The date affixed next to the “Last Updated” legend above corresponds with the date the Privacy Policy was last revised. ZeroBounce reserves the right, at any time, and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy. Any changes to the Privacy Policy will become effective when ZeroBounce posts a revised Privacy Policy. Your use of the Site and Services following any changes means that You accept the revised Privacy Policy.

NEED MORE INFORMATION OR HAVING DIFFICULTY ACCESSING THIS INFORMATION?
----------------------------------------------------------------------

If You have a disability which interferes with Your ability to access this Privacy Policy, we can make accommodations to present the Privacy Policy in an alternative format, to assist You. If You would like to receive this information in another format that is accessible to Your needs (for example: audio, large print, etc.) please contact us.

© 2023 www.zerobounce.net. All rights reserved.

© 2024 ZeroBounce.  
All rights reserved.

### Company

### Legal

### CONTACT US

* US: [1-888-500-9521](tel:+18885009521)
* EU: [+44-330-808-4814](tel:+443308084814)
* 24/7 Support Guaranteed

© 2024 ZeroBounce.  
All rights reserved.
